# JHERSON MANEJERO

# **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

O9158865167 Antipolo City Jmanejero24@gmail.com

## PROFILE

I am a creative, artistic, and ambitious Graphics Designer with a talent for thinking outside the box and coming up with innovative ideas and designs. I graduated with a degree in Information Technology from STI College and subsequently have worked in the BPO industry for the past 3 years. I pride myself in providing excellent service to all stakeholders and seeing the positive impact I make in people's lives and businesses.

# PROFESSIONAL SKILL

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Premier

- Adobe After Effect
- CSS
- HTMI

- Data Entry
- · Lead Generation
- Google Suits

# EDUCATION

### **Bachelor Of Science in Information Technology**

2015 - 2019

STI College (Cainta Campus)

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Desktop Support Engineer (Intern)**

2019

### **RJ Globus**

My Responsibility as Desktop Support Engineer is to address user tickets regarding hardware, software, and networking issues. Walking customers through installing applications and computer peripherals. Asking targeted questions to diagnose problems. Conduct remote troubleshooting and so on.

### **Data Services Associate**

2019 - 2021

### **Boldr**

As a Data Services Associate, I am responsible for executing projects of varying natures from as simple as data entry. Also responsible for auditing magazines through images that will be sent by our client via the tools that we used. Arranging Items from the correct positioning via images. Lead Generation searching for different people for possible clients that sent by our clients.

# **Graphic Designer**

2021 - 2023

#### **Boldr**

My responsibilities as a Graphic Designer are editing videos, photo editing, thumbnail creations, and Banner Ads. Mostly the work that was given to me is Video Editing, Simple Photo Editing, and Thumbnails.